Amanda Marquis
COS470
Assignment 4 



Part 1
New Chess piece - the Marquis
character = 'ℳ' (It is a fancy M, if you can't see it.. )
Movement - Combines knight/bishop type of movement. 
	It can move an odd number of spaces in one direction, and an even in the other (in respect to XY)
	Even number of spaces in the X - odd number of spaces in the Y, and vice versa
	Or, one single square in any diagonal directions.
	Captures opposite colored pieces,


Part 2
I made a human chess player (MarquisPlayer)
-It can enter its name
-It uses the black piece
-It can choose its moves... but it doesn't know what the moves are. Blind chess! Expert level chess? (Still better at chess than I am)
-Error checks the user input to be in the correct range (between 1 and the max # of moves) and a number